<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Disliked>
  <Quotes id="146">"I have learned over the years that when one’s mind is made up, this diminishes fear.  Rosa Parks</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="147">"I would rather die of passion than of boredom.  Vincent van Gogh</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="148">"You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it." -Margaret Thatcher</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="149">"I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="150">"Much of the stress that people feel doesn’t come from having too much to do. It comes from not finishing what they’ve started." -David Allen</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="151">"Focus on the journey, not the destination. Joy is found not in finishing an activity but in doing it." -Greg Anderson</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="152">"Success at the highest level comes down to one question: Can you decide that your happiness can come from someone else’s success? —Bill Walton</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="153">"Do what you have always done and you’ll get what you have always got." -Sue Knight</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="154">"Think of what you have rather than of what you lack. Of the things you have, select the best and then reflect how eagerly you would have sought them if you did not have them." -Marcus Aurelius</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="155">"Happiness is where we find it, but very rarely where we seek it." -J. Petit Senn</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="156">"You never regret being kind." -Nicole Shepherd</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="157">"To be content means that you realize you contain what you seek." -Alan Cohen</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="158">"Expecting life to treat you well because you are a good person is like expecting an angry bull not to charge because you are a vegetarian." -Shari R. Barr</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="159">"Boredom is the feeling that everything is a waste of time… serenity, that nothing is." -Thomas Szasz</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="160">"To handle yourself, use your head; to handle others, use your heart." -</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="161">"The mediocre teacher tells. The good teacher explains. The superior teacher demonstrates. The great teacher inspires." -William Arthur Ward</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="162">"It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change." -Charles Darwin</Quotes>
  <Quotes id="163">"A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty.  Unknown</Quotes>
  <Quotes ID="19">"What’s money? A man is a success if he gets up in the morning and goes to bed at night and in between does what he wants to do.  Bob Dylan</Quotes>
  <Quotes ID="20">"A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new.  </Quotes>
</Disliked>