<GetwellSoon>
    <Quotes id="1">I heard that you are in the hospital. I hope they release you soon because we need you more than they do! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="2">Don't think of it as a hospital stay. Think of it as a spa package that includes meals, regular health evaluations, and jello cubes. (Miss you!) </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="3">I want your recovery to be faster than a child running to buy ice cream on a hot summer day! Get well soon buddy! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="4">I hope you feel a little better every day. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="5">Hang in there, better days are coming. I hope each new day brings you closer to a full recovery!</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="6"> Wishing you a speedy recovery. I hope you feel better soon. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="7">Just a quick note to let you know you're in our thoughts and hoping for a speedy recovery</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="8"> It's been so lovely seeing you every day, with your humor and kindness, but it has been so sad not seeing you. Being ill and out of commission is hard on anyone. Everyone here sends best wishes for your health and healing. Take all the time you need to get well, and know that, when you return, there will be many happy faces waiting to greet you. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="9">Get well soon! Everyone here misses your contagious smile. Nothing has been the same since you became ill. No one tells a joke as you do, so please hurry and get well fast! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="10">When I think of you, the word 'strong' immediately comes to mind. Use that strength to get well soon, my friend. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="11">Get well soon! Your family and friends miss you a lot and I look forward to your return. We all send our best prayers to you, and want you to know that you are greatly missed! So, take good care and return to us soon.  </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="12"> Thinking of you, praying for you, missing you '¦ hoping you're getting better each and every day.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="13"> The old song goes ''¦ain't no sunshine when you're gone'¦'? We miss your sunshine so get better and get back to us really soon, okay?</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="14"> I heard about your sickness yesterday, and I want to let you know that I miss you and wish you a quick recovery. Know that I am really praying for you.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="15"> Hope you're out of the hospital soon, though I know you'll miss those complimentary massages. What ' you didn't get the massage? </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="16">I suffer as you suffer. Let's face it together and fight it out. Get well soon, my dear. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="17">Now that you're sick, at least try to make the best of your time and do something creative! Like watching cat videos on the internet! On a more serious note. Try to get some rest so we can have you back as soon as possible Get well soon! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="18">I wish I could take away your discomfort but, instead of that, please know that I'm thinking of you and cheering you on to a speedy recovery. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="19">Your absence is hurting me, my friend. I can't wait to see you feeling well, and I know many others are praying for your quick recovery as well, and longing for the day you will come back home. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="20">Sending you love, well wishes, prayers, and every kind of good energy to bring you back to health as soon as possible. Love you!  </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="21"> People here are missing you so much, especially your kindness and humor. Please recover quickly from your illness. We are praying for you day and night, friend.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="22"> I'd like to give you a big sloppy kiss to make you feel better, but then I'd get your germs. So, I'm sending an imaginary get well hug! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="23">May your illness pass as harmless as a summer breeze my friend. Can't wait to have you back! Get well soon! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="24">I was so sorry to hear that you were taken to the hospital last night. Let me convey my best wishes for a quick recovery from your illness, my friend.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="25"> Get well soon, so you can once again experience all the fun and delight that life has to offer! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="26">Best wishes. I hope that you're back in the swing of things very soon. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="27">The little flowers are rising and blooming; it's the world's way of saying, 'get well soon.' </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="28">From dawn to dusk, I pray for your quick recovery and good health. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="29">It seems that 'get well' isn't quite enough to say, so I'll add a 'SOON' so you'll come on out and play. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="30">Sending you well wishes for your quick recovery and good health.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="31">Get well soon so you can resume bringing brightness and delight into our lives!</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="32"> I will continue praying for your good health and speedy recovery. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="33">I know how annoying your condition is, and it's terrible to see you like this. My thoughts and prayers are with you, my I hope you get well soon! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="34">May you be blessed with good health and a quick recovery. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="35">Say goodbye to that bout of ill health, and get well soon. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="36">The most important thing when facing illness is that no matter how bad it gets, you should never lose hope. Faith is the first step to recovery. Get well soon my friend!</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="37"> Since you're under the weather, take this time to practice meditation and spiritual focus. Or you can just torment your cat. Feel better soon! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="38">Everyone here at work is doing our best to 'hold down the fort' while you're recuperating, but there's a severe shortage of fun! Come back soon, please! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="39">You've always taken such good care of me, so I'd be privileged to hasten your recovery in any way. What do you need to get better? Let me know, sweet friend. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="40">It's terrible to see you so unwell! Get well soon! I know I'll be delighted when you do, and I'm sure you will too! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="41">Don't worry; we're here to stand alongside you as you work to recapture your good health. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="42">Get ready: it's time for you to get well soon. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="43">I wish I were a magician so I could make you fit and healthy with the wave of a wand! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="44">I will stand beside you always. Wishing you good health and a fast recovery. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="45">Feel better fast so I can see you again soon! I miss you so much!</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="46"> I hope you get well really soon! I miss your smile! I pray God heals you quickly with His miraculously healing hands.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="47">Don't worry: you will be back on your feet in no time, and then you will be wishing you were off your feet again, resting! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="48">Think happy thoughts, and you may heal more quickly than you thought possible. We miss you, and want you better soon! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="49">You can get better fast! Just do it! Be well! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="50">I am sorry to hear of this tough time for you. You're in my prayers. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="51">Know this too will pass. May you heal ever so easy and fast. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="52">I hope you feel better really fast. I'm counting the days until I can see you again! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="53">I heard you were in pain. Well, don't focus on it (LOL, as I mention it). No, really: think pleasant I love ya! Get well soon! </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="54">Remember to just take it one day at a time, and, in no time, you will be completely healthy and smiling once again. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="55">I hope this 'get well' message brings a smile to your face. You are too beautiful to be feeling down. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="56">Do what the doctor says, and feel better soon! I can't wait to see you again. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="57">I ache every second you are sick, and pretty soon I am going to be in that hospital bed next to you. Get better fast, because, even though I love you, I don't want to join you. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="58">You will do more than just get better; you will be better than you were before. I can't wait to see you soon in full health. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="59">Focus on the future and concentrate on getting well. Here's to good things happening in your life. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="60">May every cell in your body heal miraculously fast. Know that you are missed greatly.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="61">May God bless you with good health and peace through this hard time. Know that I am here for you if you ever need anything. If you ever need to talk, I am always here to listen. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="62">May your tears of sorrow quickly become tears of joy. I am so sorry you aren't feeling well. I pray you to recover to full health soon. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="63">Think healthy, lovely, beautiful thoughts, and may your ails cease to exist. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="64">Even Superman has a weakness. Though you are feeling weak now, know that you will be strong again. Until then, may peace be with you. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="65">I would wish you well, but I know you don't need any wishes because you WILL be better soon. This is me letting you know that I'm thinking about you. </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="66">Sending you tons of good wishes for your fast recovery.</Quotes>
</GetwellSoon>
