<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Motivational_Quotes>
    <General>
        <Quotes id="1">"People often say that motivation doesn't last. Well, neither does bathing  that's why we recommend it daily." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="2">"The best leaders are those most interested in surrounding themselves with assistants and associates smarter than they are. They are frank in admitting this and are willing to pay for such talents." -Antos Parrish</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="3">"Beware of monotony; it's the mother of all the deadly sins." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="4">"Keep your fears to yourself, but share your courage with others." -Robert Louis Stevenson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="5">"The greatest leader is not necessarily the one who does the greatest things. He is the one that gets people to do the greatest things." -Ronald Reagan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="6">"I can’t change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination." -Jimmy Dean</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="7">"Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="8">"I cannot trust a man to control others who cannot control himself." -Robert E. Lee</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="9">"Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence." -Vince Lombardi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="10">"You get in life what you have the courage to ask for." -Nancy D. Solomon</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="11">"In the end, it is important to remember that we cannot become what we need to be by remaining what we are." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="12">"Believe you can and you’re halfway there." -Theodore Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="13">"Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears." -Les Brown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="14">"If you really want the key to success, start by doing the opposite of what everyone else is doing." -Brad Szollose</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="15">"I have learned over the years that when one’s mind is made up, this diminishes fear." -Rosa Parks</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="16">"Victory has a hundred fathers and defeat is an orphan." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="17">"Management is doing things right; leadership is doing the right things." -Peter F. Drucker</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="18">"Example is not the main thing in influencing others. It is the only thing." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="19">"Leaders must be close enough to relate to others, but far enough ahead to motivate them." -John C. Maxwell</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="20">"The mark of a great man is one who knows when to set aside the important things in order to accomplish the vital ones." -Brandon Sanderson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="21">"If you want to lift yourself up, lift up someone else." -Booker T. Washington</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="22">"You have to be burning with an idea, or a problem, or a wrong that you want to right. If you’re not passionate enough from the start, you’ll never stick it out." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="23">"A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new." -Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="24">"The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be." -Ralph Waldo Emerson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="25">"We can’t help everyone, but everyone can help someone." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="26">"Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear." -George Addair</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="27">"Being responsible sometimes means pissing people off." -Colin Powell</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="28">"Change your thoughts and you change your world." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="29">"How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world." -Anne Frank</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="30">"Nothing is really work unless you would rather be doing something else." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="31">"Without a customer, you don't have a business  all you have is a hobby." -Don Peppers</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="32">"To be most effective in sales today, it's imperative to drop your &amp;#8216;sales' mentality and start working with your prospects as if they've already hired you." -Jill Konrath</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="33">"Pretend that every single person you meet has a sign around his or her neck that says, &amp;#8216;Make me feel important.' Not only will you succeed in sales, you will succeed in life." -Mary Kay Ash</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="34">"Nothing ever gets easier. You just get stronger. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="35">"You can’t see the full picture when you are in the frame. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="36">"I will allow life’s changes to make me better, not bitter. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="37">"Wanting to be someone you’re not is the waste of the person you are. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="38">"I will not let anyone walk through my mind with their dirty feet. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="39">"Nobody can hurt me without my permission. ~Gandhi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="40">"You must be the change you wish to see in this world. ~Gandhi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="41">"&amp;#8220;It's not just about being better. It's about being different. You need to give people a reason to choose your business." -Tom Abbott</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="42">"Being good in business is the most fascinating kind of art. Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="43">"Grit is that ‘extra something' that separates the most successful people from the rest. It's the passion, perseverance, and stamina that we must channel in order to stick with our dreams until they become a reality." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="44">"The miracle is not that we do this work, but that we are happy to do it.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="45">"“Never give up on a dream just because of the time it will take to accomplish it. The time will pass anyway.” – Earl Nightingale</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="46">"“If you work on something a little bit every day, you end up with something that is massive.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="47">"“The big secret in life is that there is no secret. Whatever your goal, you can get there if you’re willing to work.” – Oprah Winfrey</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="48">"“If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="49">"“Never allow a person to tell you no who doesn’t have the power to say yes.” – Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="50">"“At any given moment you have the power to say: this is not how the story is going to end.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="51">"“Amateus sit around and wait for inspiration. The rest of us just get up and go to work.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="52">"“Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven’t found it yet, keep looking. Don’t settle. As with all matters of the heart, you’ll know when you find it.” – Steve Jobs</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="53">"“Nothing will work unless you do.” – Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="54">"“Sometimes when you’re in a dark place you think you’ve been buried but you’ve actually been planted.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="55">"Dreams don’t work unless you do.” – John C. Maxwell</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="56">"“Go the extra mile. It’s never crowded there.” – Dr. Wayne D. Dyer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="57">"Failure after long perseverance is much grander than never to have a striving good enough to be called a failure." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="58">"Nothing is impossible, the word itself says “I’m possible”!  Audrey Hepburn</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="59">"I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.  Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="60">"Whether you think you can or you think you can’t, you’re right.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="61">"Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence.  Vince Lombardi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="62">"Life is 10 percent what happens to me and 90 percent of how I react to it.  Charles Swindoll</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="63">"If you look at what you have in life, you’ll always have more. If you look at what you don’t have in life, you’ll never have enough.  Oprah Winfrey</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="64">"None of us is as smart as all of us.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="65">"I can’t change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination.  Jimmy Dean</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="66">"Believe you can and you’re halfway there.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="67">"To handle yourself, use your head; to handle others, use your heart.  Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="68">"Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.  Les Brown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="69">"Alone, we can do so little; together we can do so much.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="70">"Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.  Napoleon Hill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="71">"Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn’t do than by the ones you did do, so throw off the bowlines, sail away from safe harbor, catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore, Dream, Discover.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="72">"&amp;nbsp;“Keep your face always toward the sunshine – and shadows will fall behind you.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="73">"“What defines us is how well we rise after falling.” – Lionel from Maid in Manhattan Movie</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="74">"H.O.P.E. = Hold On. Pain Ends.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="75">"Make each day your masterpiece. – John Wooden</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="76">"“Wherever you go, go with all your heart” – Confucius</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="77">"“Turn your wounds into wisdom” – Oprah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="78">"“We can do anything we want to if we stick to it long enough.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="79">"“Begin anywhere.” – John Cage</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="80">"“Don’t limit your challenges. Challenge your limits.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="81">"“Whenever you find yourself doubting how far you can go, just remember how far you have come.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="82">"“Everyone has inside them a piece of good news. The good news is you don’t know how great you can be! How much you can love! What you can accomplish! And what your potential is.” – Anne Frank</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="83">"“Some luck lies in not getting what you thought you wanted but getting what you have, which once you have got it you may be smart enough to see is what you would have wanted had you known.” – Garrison Keillor</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="84">"“Don’t quit yet, the worst moments are usually followed by the most beautiful silver linings. You have to stay strong, remember to keep your head up and remain hopeful.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="85">"“When written in Chinese the word “crisis” is composed of two characters – one represents danger and the other represents opportunity.” –</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="86">"I’ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I’ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times I’ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I’ve failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed.  Michael Jordan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="87">"Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.  Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="88">"I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.  Stephen Covey</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="89">"When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it. &amp;#8211;Henry Ford</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="90">"The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don’t have any.  Alice Walker</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="91">"The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="92">"Teamwork is the ability to work together toward a common vision, the ability to direct individual accomplishments toward organizational objectives. It is the fuel that allows common people to attain uncommon results.  Andrew Carnegie</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="93">"Don’t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.  Robert Louis Stevenson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="94">"Do not wait; the time will never be just right.” — George Herbert, poet</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="95">"“Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.” — Les Brown, </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="96">"“If you can dream it, You can do it.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="97">"“The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.” — Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="98">"“Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can.” — Arthur Ashe</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="99">"“Aim for the moon. If you miss, you may hit a star.” — W. Clement Stone, businessman</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="100">"“Only I can change my life. No one can do it for me.” — Carol Burnett, actress</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="101">"“Do one thing every day that scares you.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="102">"“The most beautiful thing you can wear is confidence.” — Blake Lively, actress</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="103">"What we achieve inwardly will change outer reality." -Plutarch</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="104">"A good plan violently executed now is better than a perfect plan executed next week." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="105">"Feeling gratitude and not expressing it is like wrapping a present and not giving it." -William Arthur Ward</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="106">"Silent gratitude isn’t very much to anyone." -Gertrude Stein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="107">"The only people with whom you should try to get even are those who have helped you." -John E. Southard</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="108">"Keep your eyes open and try to catch people in your company doing something right, then praise them for it." -Tom Hopkins</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="109">"You wouldn’t worry so much about what others think of you if you realized how seldom they do." -Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="110">"Shyness has a strange element of narcissism, a belief that how we look, how we perform, is truly important to other people." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="111">"Do or do not. There is no try." -Yoda</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="112">"Rarely have I seen a situation where doing less than the other guy is a good strategy." -Jimmy Spithill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="113">"You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it." -Margaret Thatcher</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="114">"The best revenge is massive success." -Frank Sinatra</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="115">"The question isn’t who is going to let me; it’s who is going to stop me." -Ayn Rand</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="116">"The only way to do great work is to love what you do." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="117">"If you would convince a man that he does wrong, do right. But do not care to convince him. Men will believe what they see. Let them see." -Henry David Thoreau</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="118">"“It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.” — Confucius</Quotes>
    </General>
    <Entrepreneur>
        <Quotes id="119">"“Look up at the stars and not down at your feet. Try to make sense of what you see, and wonder about what makes the universe exist. Be curious.” — Stephen Hawking, theoretical physicist</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="120">"Try to be a rainbow in someone’s cloud.” — Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="121">"“That which doesn’t kill us makes us stronger.” — Friedrich Nietzsche</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="122">"“Believe you can and you’re halfway there.” — Theodore Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="123">"“Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="124">"“Successful entrepreneurs are givers and not takers of positive energy.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="125">"“An attitude of positive expectation is the mark of the superior personality.” — Brian Tracy, public speaker</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="126">"“Impossible is just an opinion, don’t buy it.” —&amp;nbsp; Robin Sharma, writer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="127">"“Keep your face always toward the sunshine—and shadows will fall behind you.” — Walt Whitman, American poet</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="128">"“The glow of one warm thought is to me worth more than money.” —</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="129">"“When the sun is shining I can do anything; no mountain is too high, no trouble too difficult to overcome.” — Wilma Rudolph, American track and field athlete</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="130">"“Each day provides its own gifts.” — Marcus Aurelius, philosopher</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="131">"“Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success. If you love what you are doing, you will be successful.” — Albert Schweitzer, theologian</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="132">"“Sometimes you will never know the value of a moment, until it becomes a memory.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="133">"“The most wasted of days is one without laughter.” — E. E. Cummings, American poet</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="134">"“With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts”." - Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="135">"“The secret of getting ahead is getting started.” — Mark Twain, writer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="136">"“Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does.” — William James, American philosopher</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="137">" is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts.” — Winston Churchill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="138">"“You must do the things you think you cannot do.” — Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="139">"The real opportunity for success lies within the person and not in the job.  Zig Ziglar</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="140">"Change your thoughts and you change your world.  Norman Vincent Peale</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="141">"There is no royal road to anything. One thing at a time, all things in succession. That which grows fast, withers as rapidly. That which grows slowly, endures.  Josiah Gilbert Holland</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="142">"Be not afraid of life. Believe that life is worth living, and your belief will help create the fact.  William James</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="143">"Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs.  Farrah Gray</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="144">"Remember that not getting what you want is sometimes a wonderful stroke of luck.  Dalai Lama</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="145">"You can’t use up creativity. The more you use, the more you have.  Maya Angelou</Quotes>
    </Entrepreneur>
    <Student>
        <Quotes id="146">"I have learned over the years that when one’s mind is made up, this diminishes fear.  Rosa Parks</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="147">"I would rather die of passion than of boredom.  Vincent van Gogh</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="148">"You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it." -Margaret Thatcher</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="149">"I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="150">"Much of the stress that people feel doesn’t come from having too much to do. It comes from not finishing what they’ve started." -David Allen</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="151">"Focus on the journey, not the destination. Joy is found not in finishing an activity but in doing it." -Greg Anderson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="152">"Success at the highest level comes down to one question: Can you decide that your happiness can come from someone else’s success? —Bill Walton</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="153">"Do what you have always done and you’ll get what you have always got." -Sue Knight</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="154">"Think of what you have rather than of what you lack. Of the things you have, select the best and then reflect how eagerly you would have sought them if you did not have them." -Marcus Aurelius</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="155">"Happiness is where we find it, but very rarely where we seek it." -J. Petit Senn</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="156">"You never regret being kind." -Nicole Shepherd</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="157">"To be content means that you realize you contain what you seek." -Alan Cohen</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="158">"Expecting life to treat you well because you are a good person is like expecting an angry bull not to charge because you are a vegetarian." -Shari R. Barr</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="159">"Boredom is the feeling that everything is a waste of time… serenity, that nothing is." -Thomas Szasz</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="160">"To handle yourself, use your head; to handle others, use your heart." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="161">"The mediocre teacher tells. The good teacher explains. The superior teacher demonstrates. The great teacher inspires." -William Arthur Ward</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="162">"It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change." -Charles Darwin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="163">"A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty.  Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="164">"A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new.  </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="165">"What’s money? A man is a success if he gets up in the morning and goes to bed at night and in between does what he wants to do.  Bob Dylan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="166">"I have been impressed with the urgency of doing. Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Being willing is not enough; we must do.  Leonardo da Vinci</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="167">"If you want to lift yourself up, lift up someone else.  Booker T. Washington</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="168">"When I stand before God at the end of my life, I would hope that I would not have a single bit of talent left and could say, I used everything you gave me.  Erma Bombeck</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="169">"The quickest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it back in your pocket.  Will Rogers</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="170">"Certain things catch your eye, but pursue only those that capture the heart.  Ancient Indian Proverb</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="171">"When I hear somebody sigh, ‘Life is hard,’ I am always tempted to ask, ‘Compared to what?’”  Sydney Harris</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="172">"Everything has beauty, but not everyone can see.  Confucius</Quotes>
    </Student>
    <Quotes id="173">"Nurture your mind with great thoughts. To believe in the heroic makes heroes.  Benjamin Disraeli</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="174">"When I was 5 years old, my mother always told me that happiness was the key to life. When I went to school, they asked me what I wanted to be when I grew up. I wrote down “happy”. They told me I didn’t understand the assignment, and I told them they didn’t understand life.  John Lennon</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="175">"The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.  Ralph Waldo Emerson</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="176">"We can’t help everyone, but everyone can help someone.  </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="177">"If you want to build a ship, don’t drum up the men to gather wood, divide the work and give orders. Instead, teach them to yearn for the vast and endless sea.” – Antoine de Saint-Exupery</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="178">"You are not in the universe, you are the universe, an intrinsic part of it. Ultimately you are not a person, but a focal point where the universe is becoming conscious of itself. What an amazing miracle.” – Eckhart Tolle</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="179">"We do not see things as they are, we see things as we are.” – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="180">"You are a child of the universe, no less than the trees and the stars; you have a right to be here.” – Max Ehrmann</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="181">"Fairytales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten.” – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="182">"There is nothing noble in being superior to your fellow men, true nobility is being superior to your former self.” – Ernest Hemingway</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="183">"The nitrogen in our DNA, the calcium in our teeth, the iron in our blood, the carbon in our apple pies was made in the interiors of collapsing stars. We are made of star-stuff.” – Carl Sagan</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="184">"We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be.” – Kurt Vonnegut</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="185">"When we love, we always strive to become better than we are. When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better too.” – Paulo Coelho</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="186">"If you’re reading this… Congratulations, you’re alive. If that’s not something to smile about, then I don’t know what is.” – Chad Sugg</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="187">"I will love the light for it shows me the way, yet I will endure the darkness because it shows me the stars.” – Og Mandino</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="188">"Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear." -George Addair</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="189">"We can easily forgive a child who is afraid of the dark; the real tragedy of life is when men are afraid of the light." -Plato</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="190">"Nothing will work unless you do." -Maya Angelou</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="191">"I alone cannot change the world, but I can cast a stone across the water to create many ripples." -Mother Teresa</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="192">"What we achieve inwardly will change outer reality." -Plutarch</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="193">"The secret of joy in work is contained in one word  excellence. To know how to do something well is to enjoy it." -Pearl Buck</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="194">"Develop success from failures. Discouragement and failure are two of the surest stepping stones to success." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="195">"Action is the foundational key to all success." -Pablo Picasso</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="196">"The ladder of success is best climbed by stepping on the rungs of opportunity." -Ayn Rand</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="197">"Formula for success: rise early, work hard, strike oil." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="198">"The difference between a successful person and others is not a lack of strength, not a lack of knowledge, but rather a lack of will." -Vince Lombardi</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="199">"Obstacles are those frightful things you see when you take your eyes off your goal." -Henry Ford</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="200">"It is your determination and persistence that will make you a successful person." -Kenneth J Hutchins</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="201">"You can waste your lives drawing lines. Or you can live your life crossing them." -Shonda Rhimes</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="202">"vational quote by Shonda Rhimes</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="203">"Determine that the thing can and shall be done, and then we shall find the way." -Abraham Lincoln</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="204">"Done is better than perfect." -Sheryl Sandberg</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="205">"Don't ask if your dream is crazy, ask if it's crazy enough." -Lena Waithe</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="206">"The act of doing something un-does the fear." -Shonda Rhimes</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="207">"Be poor, humble and driven (PhD). Don't be afraid to shift or pivot." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="208">"Someday is not a day of the week." -Denise Brennan-Nelson</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="209">"Hire character. Train skill." -Peter Schutz</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="210">"Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life." -Steve Jobs</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="211">"Sales are contingent upon the attitude of the salesman  not the attitude of the prospect." -W. Clement Stone</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="212">"Everyone lives by selling something." -Robert Louis Stevenson</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="213">"If you are not taking care of your customer, your competitor will." -Bob Hooey</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="214">"The golden rule for every businessman is this: Put yourself in your customer's place." -Orison Swett Marden</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="215">"If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way." -Napoleon Hill</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="216">"Be patient with yourself. Self-growth is tender; it's holy ground. There's no greater investment." -Stephen Covey</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="217">"Without hustle, talent will only carry you so far." -Gary Vaynerchuk</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="218">"Love For All, Hatred For None. – Khalifatul Masih III</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="219">"Change the world by being yourself. – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="220">"Every moment is a fresh beginning. – T.S Eliot</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="221">"Never regret anything that made you smile. – Mark Twain</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="222">"Die with memories, not dreams. – Unknown</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="223">"Aspire to inspire before we expire. – Unknown</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="224">"Everything you can imagine is real. – Pablo Picasso</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="225">"Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. – Leonardo da Vinci</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="226">"Whatever you do, do it well. – Walt Disney</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="227">"What we think, we become. – Buddha</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="228">"All limitations are self-imposed. – Oliver Wendell Holmes</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="229">"Tough times never last but tough people do. – Robert H. Schiuller</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="230">"Problems are not stop signs, they are guidelines. – Robert H. Schiuller</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="231">"One day the people that don’t even believe in you will tell everyone how they met you. – Johnny Depp</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="232">"If I’m gonna tell a real story, I’m gonna start with my name. – Kendrick Lamar</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="233">"To live will be an awfully big adventure. – Peter Pan</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="234">"Try to be a rainbow in someone’s cloud. – Maya Angelou</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="235">"There is no substitute for hard work. – Thomas Edison</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="236">"What consumes your mind controls your life- Unknown</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="237">"Strive for greatness. – Lebron James</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="238">"Wanting to be someone else is a waste of who you are. – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="239">"And still, I rise. – Maya Angelou</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="240">"The time is always right to do what is right. – Martin Luther King Jr.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="241">"Let the beauty of what you love be what you do. – Rumi</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="242">"May your choices reflect your hopes, not your fears. – Nelson Mandela</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="243">"A happy soul is the best shield for a cruel world. – Atticus</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="244">"White is not always light and black is not always dark. – Habeeb Akande</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="245">"I learned that courage was not the absence of fear, but the triumph over it. The brave man is not he who does not feel afraid, but he who conquers that fear.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="246">"If you believe it will work, you'll see opportunities. If you believe it won't, you will see obstacles.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="247">"Believe you can and you're halfway there.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="248">"Learn the rules like a pro, so you can break them like an artist.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="249">"Do one thing every day that scares you.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="250">"I didn't get there by wishing for it or hoping for it, but by working for it.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="251">"If you can dream it, you can do it.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="252">"Even if you are on the right track, you'll get run over if you just sit there.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="253">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="254">"Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="255">"Earn your leadership every day.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="256">"It's not just about being better. It's about being different. You need to give people a reason to choose your business.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="257">"The leader has to be practical and a realist yet must talk the language of the visionary and the idealist.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="258">"Leadership and learning are indispensable to each other.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="259">"The pessimist complains about the wind. The optimist expects it to change. The leader adjusts the sails.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="260">"Alone we can do so little; together we can do so much.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="261">"The way a team plays as a whole determines its success. You may have the greatest bunch of individual stars in the world, but if they don't play together, the club won't be worth a dime.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="262">"It is amazing what you can accomplish if you do not care who gets the credit.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="263">"I can do things you cannot, you can do things I cannot: together we can do great things.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="264">"Life becomes easier when you learn to accept the apology you never got. – R. Brault</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="265">"Happiness depends upon ourselves. – Aristotle</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="266">"Turn your wounds into wisdom. – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="267">"Change the game, don’t let the game change you. – Macklemore</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="268">"It hurt because it mattered. – John Green</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="269">"If the world was blind how many people would you impress? – Boonaa Mohammed</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="270">"I will remember and recover, not forgive and forget. – Unknown</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="271">"The meaning of life is to give life meaning. – Ken Hudgins</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="272">"The true meaning of life is to plant trees, under whose shade you do not expect to sit. – Nelson Henderson</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="273">"When words fail, music speaks. – Shakespeare</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="274">"Embrace the glorious mess that you are. – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="275">"Normality is a paved road: it’s comfortable to walk but no flowers grow. – Vincent van Gogh</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="276">"I have nothing to lose but something to gain. – Eminem</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="277">"If you tell the truth you don’t have to remember anything. – Mark Twain</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="278">"Have enough courage to start and enough heart to finish. – Jessica N. S. Yourko</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="279">"Hate comes from intimidation, love comes from appreciation. – Tyga</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="280">"I could agree with you but then we’d both be wrong. – Harvey Specter</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="281">"Oh, the things you can find, if you don’t stay behind. – Dr. Seuss</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="282">"Determine your priorities and focus on them. – </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="283">"Be so good they can’t ignore you. – Steve Martin</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="284">"Dream as if you’ll live forever, live as if you’ll die today. – James Dean</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="285">"Yesterday you said tomorrow. Just do it. – Nike</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="286">"You only have to be right once.” —founder of Dropbox </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="287">"“I’m not afraid to take a swing and miss.” — Fred Smith, founder of FedEx Corporation</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="288">"“When there is no struggle, there is no strength.” — Oprah Winfrey, media executive</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="289">"“Opportunities don’t happen, you create them.” — </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="290">"“Never give up. Today is hard, tomorrow will be worse, but the day after tomorrow will be sunshine.” — Jack Ma, founder of Alibaba group</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="291">"“Nothing will work unless you do.” — Maya Angelou, poet</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="292">"“If you love what you do and are willing to do what it takes, it’s within your reach.” — Steve Wozniak, co-founder of Apple Computer</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="293">"“Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible.” — </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="294">"“There’s no shortage of remarkable ideas, what’s missing is the will to execute them.” — Seth Godin, writer</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="295">"“Never, never, never give up.” — Winston Churchill, former British Prime Minister</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="296">"“Whether you think you can, or you think you can’t — You’re right.” — Henry Ford, founder of Ford Motor Company</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="297">"“Things do not happen. Things are made to happen.”&amp;nbsp; —</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="298">", former President of the United States</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="299">"“If you want to achieve greatness stop asking for permission.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="300">"“I have not failed. I’ve just found 10,000 ways that won’t work.” — Thomas A. Edison, inventor</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="301">"“The function of leadership is to produce more leaders, not more followers.” — Ralph Nader, political activist</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="302">"“I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have.” —Thomas Jefferson, former President of the United States</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="303">"“Don’t be afraid to give up the good to go for the great.” — John D. Rockefeller, business magnate</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="304">"I don’t need it to be easy, I need it to be worth it. – Lil Wayne</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="305">"Never let your emotions overpower your intelligence. – Drake</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="306">"Nothing lasts forever but at least we got these memories. – J. Cole</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="307">"Don’t you know your imperfections is a blessing? – Kendrick Lamar</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="308">"Reality is wrong, dreams are for real. – Tupac</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="309">"Working hard for something we don't care about is called stressed; working hard for something we love is called passion." -Simon Sinek</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="310">"I'd rather regret the things I've done than regret the things I haven't done." -Lucille Ball</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="311">" by Lucille Ball</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="312">"I didn't get there by wishing for it or hoping for it, but by working for it." -Estée Lauder</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="313">"Always do your best. What you plant now, you will harvest later." -Og Mandino</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="314">"The key to life is accepting challenges. Once someone stops doing this, he's dead." -Bette Davis</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="315">"Move out of your comfort zone. You can only grow if you are willing to feel awkward and uncomfortable when you try something new." -Brian Tracy</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="316">"Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful." -Joshua J. Marine</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="317">" by Joshua J. Marine</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="318">"Don't let the fear of losing be greater than the excitement of winning." -Robert Kiyosaki</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="319">"How dare you settle for less when the world has made it so easy for you to be remarkable?" -Seth Godin</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="320">"Energy and persistence conquer all things." &amp;#8211;</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="321">"Perseverance is failing 19 times and succeeding the 20th." -Julie Andrews</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="322">"Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try one more time.” — Thomas A. Edison</Quotes>

    <Fitness>
        <Quotes id="323">"Our greatest glory is not in never falling but in rising every time we fall.” — Confucius, Chinese philosopher</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="324">"“The future depends on what you do today.” — Mahatma Gandhi, pacifist</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="325">"“If you don’t have any shadows you’re not in the light.” </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="326">"“It isn’t where you came from. It’s where you’re going that counts.” — Ella Fitzgerald, jazz singer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="327">"“A ship is always safe at the shore, but that is not what it is built for.” — Albert Einstein, theoretical physicist</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="328">"“Don’t wait for the perfect conditions for success to happen; just go ahead and do something.” — Dan Miller, writer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="329">"“What seems to us as bitter trials are often blessings in disguise.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="330">", Irish poet</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="331">"“Go as far as you can see; when you get there, you’ll be able to see further.” Thomas Carlyle, Scottish historian</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="332">"“You learn more from failure than from success. Don’t let it stop you. Failure builds character.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="333">"“A river cuts through rock, not because of its power but because of its persistence.” — Jim Watkins, American journalist</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="334">"“Be so good they can’t ignore you.” — Steve Martin, actor</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="335">"“Success doesn’t come to you, you go to it.” Marva Collins, American educator</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="336">"“With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts.” — Eleanor Roosevelt, former First Lady of the United States</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="337">"“It is never too late to be what you might have been.” — George Eliot, novelist</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="338">"“If I cannot do great things, I can do small things in a great way.” — Martin Luther King Jr.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="339">"“There are no shortcuts to anywhere worth going.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="340">"“It’s not whether you get knocked down, it’s whether you get back up.” – Vince Lombardi, Football Hall of Fame coach</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="341">"“The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing.” – Walt Disney, film producer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="342">"“If you can’t fly, then run. If you can’t run, then walk. If you can’t walk, then crawl, but whatever you do, you have to keep moving forward.” – Martin Luther King, Jr., civil rights activist</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="343">"“You miss 100 percent of the shots you don’t take.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="344">"“The biggest risk is not taking any risk… In a world that’s changing really quickly, the only strategy that is guaranteed to fail is not taking risks.” — Mark Zuckerberg, co-founder of Facebook</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="345">"“Preparation is the key to success.” — Alexander Graham Bell, co-founder of AT&amp;amp;T</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="346">"“Today a reader. Tomorrow a leader.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
    </Fitness>
    <Quotes id="347">"“Many of life’s failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up.” – Thomas A. Edison</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="348">"It is the long history of humankind (and animal kind, too) that those who learned to collaborate and improvise most effectively have prevailed.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="349">"The ones who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="350">"Try to be a rainbow in someone's cloud.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="351">"Follow your bliss and the universe will open doors where there were only walls.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="352">"A year from now you may wish you had started today.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="353">"Don't count the days, make the days count.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="354">"Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="355">"Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="356">"You can’t use up creativity. The more you use, the more you have.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="357">"I would rather die of passion than of boredom.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="358">"Nothing is impossible, the word itself says “I’m possible!"</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="359">"If you look at what you have in life, you’ll always have more. If you look at what you don’t have in life, you’ll never have enough.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="360">"The only place you find success before work is in the dictionary.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="361">"Hope never abandons you, you abandon it.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="362">"Just decide; what's it's gonna be, who you're gonna be and how you're gonna do it, and then from that point, the universe will get out of your way.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="363">"Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="364">"Those who dare to fail miserably can achieve greatly.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="365">"I’m a success today because I had a friend who believed in me and I didn’t have the heart to let him down.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="366">"It is our choices, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="367">"Go until you fail, then keep going.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="368">"“Even if people are still very young, they shouldn’t be prevented from saying what they think.” ― Anne Frank, diarist</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="369">"“You can, you should, and if you’re brave enough to start, you will.” – Stephen King, writer</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="370">"“When you have a dream, you’ve got to grab it and never let go.” — Carol Burnett, actress</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="371">"It’s a good day to have a good day.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="372">"You didn’t come this far to only come this far.” — Anonymous</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="373">"“Work hard in silence, let your success be your noise.” — Frank Ocean, singer-songwriter</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="374">"“ A goal should scare you a little, and excite you a lot.” Joe Vitale, spiritual teacher</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="375">"“Don’t let yesterday take up too much of today.” — </Quotes>
    <Quotes id="376">"“Every morning starts a new page in your story. Make it a great one today.” — Doe Zantamata, author</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="377">"Don’t let the fear of striking out hold you back.” — Babe Ruth, professional baseball player</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="378">"“Believe me, the reward is not so great without the struggle.” Wilma Rudolph, track and field athlete</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="379">"“When you fall, get right back up.” — Lindsay Vonn, professional skier</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="380">"“If you don’t love what you do, you won’t do it with much conviction or passion.” — Mia Hamm, professional soccer player</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="381">"“If you aren’t going all the way, why go at all?” — Joe Namath, Football Hall of Famer</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="382">"“Obstacles don’t have to stop you. If you run into a wall, don’t turn around and give up.” — Michael Jordan, basketball icon</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="383">"“Champions keep playing until they get it right.” — Billie Jean King, Tennis Hall of Famer</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="384">"“You have to believe in yourself when no one else does.” — Venus Williams, professional tennis player</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="385">"“Always make a total effort, even when the odds are against you.” — Arnold Palmer, golf icon</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="386">"A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="387">"Don't let the noise of others' opinions drown out your own inner voice.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="388">"Age is something that doesn't matter, unless you are a cheese.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="389">"There is only one way to avoid criticism: Do nothing, say nothing, and be nothing.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="390">"If you obey all the rules, you miss all the fun.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="391">"All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="392">"Be so good they can't ignore you.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="393">"Someone is sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="394">"You are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem and smarter than you think.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="395">"Don't be pushed by your problems. Be led by your dreams.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="396">"Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="397">"Hardships often prepare ordinary people for an extraordinary destiny.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="398">"If it doesn't challenge you, it won't change you.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="399">"There is only one thing that makes a dream impossible to achieve: the fear of failure.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="400">"The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="401">"The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="402">"Success is no accident. It is hard work, perseverance, learning, studying, sacrifice and most of all, love of what you are doing or learning to do.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="403">"The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="404">"I’m not terribly interested in beauty. What touches me is someone who understands herself.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="405">"If you don’t like something, change it. If you can’t change it, change your attitude.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="406">"Power’s not given to you. You have to take it.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="407">"Beware of monotony; it’s the mother of all the deadly sins.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="408">"What you do makes a difference, and you have to decide what kind of difference you want to make.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="409">"Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn’t do than by the things you did.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="410">"It is never too late to be what you might have been.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="411">"The greatest danger for most of us is not that our aim is too high and we miss it but that it is too low and we reach it.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="412">"Life isn’t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.</Quotes>
    <Quotes id="413">"You can fall, but you can rise also.</Quotes>
    <sports>
        <Quotes id="414">"You can’t eat beauty, it doesn’t sustain you. What is fundamentally beautiful is compassion for yourself and those around you. That kind of beauty inflames the heart and enchants the soul.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="415">"“If you have everything under control, you’re not moving fast enough.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="416">", champion racing driver</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="417">"“It isn’t the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; It’s the pebble in your shoe.” — Muhammad Ali, champion boxer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="418">"“Don’t let life discourage you; everyone who got where he is had to begin where he was.” — Richard L. Evans, writer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="419">"“Go the extra mile, it’s never crowded.”— Anonymous</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="420">"“Keep your sunny side up, keep yourself beautiful, and indulge yourself.” — Betsey Johnson, fashion designer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="421">"“Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you react to it.” — </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="422">"“Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving.” — Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="423">"“Limit your ‘always’ and your ‘nevers.’” — Amy Poehler​​, comedian</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="424">"“Nothing is impossible. The word itself says ‘I’m possible!’” — Audrey Hepburn, actress</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="425">"“You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream.” — C.S. Lewis, writer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="426">"Remember that not getting what you want is sometimes a wonderful stroke of luck." -Dalai Lama</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="427">"The successful warrior is the average man, with laserlike focus." -Bruce Lee</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="428">"You can’t connect the dots looking forward; you can only connect them looking backward. So you have to trust that the dots will somehow connect in your future. You have to trust in something — your gut, destiny, life, karma, whatever. This approach has never let me down, and it has made all the difference in my life." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="429">"Successful people do what unsuccessful people are not willing to do. Don’t wish it were easier; wish you were better." -Jim Rohn</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="430">"The No. 1 reason people fail in life is because they listen to their friends, family, and neighbors." -Napoleon Hill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="431">"Many of life’s failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="432">"What would you attempt to do if you knew you would not fail? —Robert Schuller</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="433">"Always bear in mind that your own resolution to success is more important than any other one thing." -Abraham Lincoln</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="434">"These inspiring quotes can pick you up on a bad day and inspire you to greater heights. Try them now!</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="435">"The greatest effort is not concerned with results." -Atisha</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="436">"Wisdom equals knowledge plus courage. You have to not only know what to do and when to do it, but you have to also be brave enough to follow through." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="437">"In a battle between two ideas, the best one doesn’t necessarily win. No, the idea that wins is the one with the most fearless heretic behind it." -Seth Godin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="438">"Remember, teamwork begins by building trust. And the only way to do that is to overcome our need for invulnerability." -Patrick Lencioni</Quotes>
    </sports>
    <Women>
        <Quotes id="439">"Leadership is an action, not a position." -Donald McGannon</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="440">"Surround yourself with great people; delegate authority; get out of the way." -Ronald Reagan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="441">"I cannot give you a formula for success, but I can give you the formula for failure, which is: Try to please everybody." -Herbert Bayard Swope</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="442">"Show me the man you honor and I will know what kind of man you are." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="443">"A man always has two reasons for doing anything: a good reason and the real reason." -J.P. Morgan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="444">"If you spend your life trying to be good at everything, you will never be great at anything." -Tom Rath</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="445">"Average leaders raise the bar on themselves; good leaders raise the bar for others; great leaders inspire others to raise their own bar." -Orrin Woodward</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="446">"Don’t blow off another’s candle for it won’t make yours shine brighter." -Jaachynma N.E. Agu</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="447">"Whenever you see a successful business, someone once made a courageous decision." -Peter F. Drucker</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="448">"If you are not willing to risk the unusual, you will have to settle for the ordinary." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="449">"Take up one idea. Make that one idea your life-think of it, dream of it, live on that idea. Let the brain, muscles, nerves, every part of your body, be full of that idea, and just leave every other idea alone. This is the way to success." -Swami Vivekananda</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="450">"If you are willing to do more than you are paid to do, eventually you will be paid to do more than you do." -Anonymous</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="451">"Success is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm." -Winston Churchill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="452">"Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve." -Napoleon Hill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="453">"Whenever you see a successful person, you only see the public glories, never the private sacrifices to reach them." -Vaibhav Shah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="454">"Try not to become a person of success, but rather try to become a person of value." -Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="455">"When you put together deep knowledge about a subject that intensely matters to you, charisma happens. You gain courage to share your passion, and when you do that, folks follow." -Jerry Porras</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="456">"People buy into the leader before they buy into the vision." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="457">"A good leader is a person who takes a little more than his share of the blame and a little less than his share of the credit." -John Maxwell</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="458">"Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out." -Robert Collier</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="459">"The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don’t have any." -Alice Walker</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="460">"The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity." -Amelia Earhart</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="461">"It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light." -Aristotle Onassis</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="462">"Feet, what do I need you for when I have wings to fly?</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="463">"When you can’t find someone to follow, you have to find a way to lead by example.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="464">"When I dare to be powerful—to use my strength in the service of my vision—then it becomes less and less important whether I am afraid.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="465">"I realized that I don’t have to be perfect. All I have to do is show up and enjoy the messy, imperfect and beautiful journey of my life.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="466">"You may not always have a comfortable life and you will not always be able to solve all of the world’s problems at once but don’t ever underestimate the importance you can have because history has shown us that courage can be contagious and hope can take on a life of its own.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="467">"It's a philosophy of life. A practice. If you do this, something will change, what will change is that you will change, your life will change, and if you can change you, you can perhaps change the world.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="468">"Don’t let anyone rob you of your imagination, your creativity, or your curiosity. It’s your place in the world; it’s your life. Go on and do all you can with it, and make it the life you want to live.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="469">"It’s not the load that breaks you down, it’s the way you carry it.</Quotes>
    </Women>
    <Emotional>
        <Quotes id="470">"If there is a book that you want to read, but it hasn’t been written yet, you must be the one to write it.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="471">"Pain is inevitable. Suffering is optional.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="472">"Luck has nothing to do with it.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="473">"Only put off until tomorrow what you are willing to die having left undone.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="474">"There is nothing noble in being superior to your fellow men. True nobility lies in being superior to your former self.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="475">"One of the secrets of life is that all that is really worth the doing is what we do for others.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="476">"Don’t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant." -Robert Louis Stevenson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="477">"Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear — not absence of fear." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="478">"Only put off until tomorrow what you are willing to die having left undone." -Pablo Picasso</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="479">"Twenty years from now, you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn’t do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -Mark Twain</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="480">"I alone cannot change the world, but I can cast a stone across the water to create many ripples." -Mother Teresa</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="481">"Whether you think you can or you think you can’t, you’re right." -Henry Ford</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="482">"Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it." -Henry David Thoreau</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="483">"Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds discuss people." -Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="484">"I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="485">"When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it." -Henry Ford</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="486">"No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="487">"The distance between insanity and genius is measured only by success." -Bruce Feirstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="488">"Don’t be afraid to give up the good to go for the great." -</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="489">"If you can’t explain it simply, you don’t understand it well enough." -Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="490">"There are two types of people who will tell you that you cannot make a difference in this world: those who are afraid to try and those who are afraid you will succeed." -Ray Goforth</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="491">"You shouldn't dream your film, you should make it!</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="492">"Nothing will work unless you do.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="493">"Decide whether or not the goal is worth the risks involved. If it is, stop worrying.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="494">"Find something you're passionate about and keep tremendously interested in it.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="495">"I have not failed. I’ve just found 10,000 ways that won’t work.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="496">"Where there is love and inspiration, I don't think you can go wrong.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="497">"Love the life you live. Live the life you love.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="498">"Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see a shadow.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="499">"You must do the things you think you cannot do.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="500">"Smile and the world smiles with you.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="501">"If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="502">"I'm not trying to do something different, I'm trying to do the same thing but in a different way.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="503">"There is no better designer than nature.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="504">"Every birthday is a gift. Every day is a gift.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="505">"The reality is: sometimes you lose. And you’re never too good to lose. You’re never too big to lose. You’re never too smart to lose. It happens.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="506">"In the midst of chaos, there is also opportunity.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="507">"Be kind whenever possible. It is always possible. ~Dalai Lama</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="508">"First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win. ~Gandhi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="509">"In a gentle way you can shake the world. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="510">"The truth will set you free but first, it’ll piss you off. ~Gloria Steinem</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="511">"If you want to be happy, be. ~Kozma Prutkov</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="512">"What if I fall. But my darling, what if you fly? ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="513">"You are confined only by the walls you build yourself. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="514">"Nothing ever goes away until it has taught us what we need to know. ~Pema Chödrön</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="515">"It is better to light a candle than to curse the darkness. ~Chinese Proverb</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="516">"The lust for comfort kills the passions of the soul. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="517">"But let there be spaces in your togetherness, and let the winds of the heavens dance between you. Love one another but make not a bond of love: let it rather be a moving sea between the shores of your souls. ~Khalil Gibran</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="518">"One day you will ask me which is more important? My life or yours? I will say mine and you will walk away not knowing that you are my life. ~Khalil Gibran</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="519">"And forget not that the earth delights to feel your bare feet and the winds long to play with your hair. ~Khalil Gibran</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="520">"When you love you should not think you can direct the course of love, for love, if it finds you worthy, directs your course. ~Khalil Gibran</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="521">"Love is what we were born with. Fear is what we learned here. ~Marianne Williamson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="522">"If you’re too busy to sit still for 10 minutes, you need to sit still for an hour. ~Zen proverb</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="523">"I saw the angel in the marble and carved until I set him free. ~Michelangelo</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="524">"It takes courage to grow up and turn out to be who you really are. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="525">"Doubt kills more dreams than failure ever will. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="526">"“It’s impossible.” said Pride. “It’s risky.” said Experience. “It’s pointless.” said Reason. “Give it a try!” whispered the Heart.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="527">"All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to us. ~J.R.R. Tolkien</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="528">"All that is gold does not glitter, Not all those who wander are lost; The old that is strong does not wither, Deep roots are not reached by the frost. ~J.R.R Tolkien</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="529">"Even the smallest person can change the course of the future. ~J.R.R Tolkien</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="530">"Two things define you: Your patience when you have nothing and your attitude when you have everything. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="531">"As is a tale, so is life. Not how long it is but how good it is that matters. ~Seneca</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="532">"To thine own self, be true. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="533">"We cannot start over but we can begin now and make a new ending. ~Zig Ziglar</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="534">"What you allow is what will continue. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="535">"If you don’t like where you are, move. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="536">"The wound is where the light enters you. ~Rumi</Quotes>
    </Emotional>
    <Chasing_Dream>
        <Quotes id="537">"You will never reach your destination if you stop and throw stones at every dog that barks. ~Winston Churchill</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="538">"I gave up complaining and gained a whole new life. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="539">"You must not lose faith in humanity. Humanity is an ocean. If a few drops of ocean are dirty, the ocean does not become dirty.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="540">"The problem with the world is that we draw our family circle too close. ~Mother Teresa</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="541">"I have found the paradox that if you love until it hurts, there can be no more hurt. Only love. ~Mother Teresa</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="542">"You don’t get a good life or a bad life. You get a life. Good or bad is up to you. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="543">"Everything I thought I was being rejected for something good, I was being redirected to something better. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="544">"It is our choices that show what we truly are far more than our ability. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="545">"It is impossible to live without failing at something, unless you live so cautiously that you might as well not have lived at all, in which case you have failed by default. ~J.K. Rowling</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="546">"It matters not what someone is born but what they grow to be. ~J.K. Rowling</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="547">"Forgiveness means letting go of the hope for a better past. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="548">"What is love? Love is the absence of judgement. ~Dalai Lama</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="549">"My religion is kindness. ~Dalai Lama</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="550">"Student says: “I’m very discouraged. What should I do?” Master says: “Encourage others.” ~ Zen Proverb</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="551">"Let go or be dragged. ~Zen Proverb</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="552">"You will get all that you want in life if you help enough other people get what they want. ~ Zig Ziglar</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="553">"Failure is an event, not a person. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="554">"People often say motivation doesn’t last. Neither does bathing—that’s why we recommend it daily. ~Zig Ziglar</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="555">"It is an undoubted truth, that the less one has to do, the less time one finds to do it in. ~Earl of Chesterfield</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="556">"We must all suffer one of two things: the pain of discipline or the pain of regret and disappointment. ~ Jim Rohn</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="557">"And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom. ~Anaïs Nin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="558">"We don’t see things as they are, we see them as we are. ~Anaïs Nin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="559">"The role of a writer is not to say what we can all say, but what we are unable to say. ~Anaïs Nin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="560">"You cannot save people. You can only love them. ~Anaïs Nin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="561">"Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one’s courage. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="562">"Worry does not empty tomorrow of its sorrow. It empties today of its strength. Corrie ten Boom</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="563">"Everyone is fighting a battle you know nothing about. Always be kind. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="564">"Don’t bring negative to my door. ~Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="565">"When people show you who they are, believe them. ~Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="566">"There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you. ~Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="567">"We do the best we can with what we have and when we know better, we do better. ~Maya Angelou</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="568">"I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.― </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="569">"Don’t be reckless with other people’s hearts. Don’t put up with people who are reckless with yours. ~Mary Schmich</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="570">"Raise your words, not your voice. It is rain that grow flowers, not thunder. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="571">"On this path, let the heart be your guide. For the body is resistant and full of fear. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="572">"Do not be satisfied with the stories that have gone before you. Unfold your own path. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="573">"What you seek is seeking you. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="574">"Your task is not to seek for love but to seek and find all the barriers you have built against it. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="575">"If you are irritated by every rub, how will you ever be polished? ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="576">"The entrance door to the sanctuary is inside you. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="578">"Whatever you lost through fate, be certain that it saved you from pain. ~Rumi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="579">"You discover you have wings when you open a book. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="580">"When you’re happy, don’t promise. When you’re angry, don’t answer. When you’re upset, don’t decide. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="581">"No matter how far you have gone on the wrong road, turn back. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="582">"Do or do not. There is no try. ~Yoda</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="583">"Faith is to believe what you do not see; the reward of this faith is to see what you believe. ~St. Augustine</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="584">"Your job is not to judge. Your job is not to figure out if someone deserves something. Your job is to lift the fallen, to restore the broken and to heal the hurting. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="585">"I used to think the worst thing in life is to end up all alone. It isn’t. the worst thing in life is to end up with people who make you feel all alone. ~Robin Williams</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="586">"Writing is a lonely job. Having someone who believes in you makes a lot of difference. They don’t have to make speeches. Just believing is usually enough. ~Stephen King</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="587">"Now comes the big question: What are you going to write about? And the equally big answer: Anything you damn well want. Anything at all …. as long as you tell the truth. ~Stephen King</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="588">"Do you need someone to make you a paper badge with the word WRITER on it before you can believe you are one? God I hope not. ~Stephen King</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="589">"You must not come lightly to the blank page. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="590">"If you don’t have the time to read, you don’t have the time or the tools to write. ~Stephen King</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="591">"Anyone who thought high school was the best time of their life is totally fucked up. ~Stephen King</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="592">"Talent is cheaper than table salt. What separates the talented individual from the successful one is a lot of hard work. ~Stephen King</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="593">"Be strong when you are weak, brave when you are scared and humble when you are victorious. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="594">"For 37 years I’ve practiced 14 hours a day, and now they call me a genius. ~Pablo de Sarasate</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="595">"It always seems impossible until it’s done. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="596">"Resentment is like drinking poison and then hoping it will kill your enemies. ~Nelson Mandela</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="597">"I’m not dismissing the value of higher education; I’m simply saying it comes at the expense of experience. ~Steve Jobs</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="598">"You’ve been criticising yourself for years and it hasn’t worked. Try approving of yourself and see what happens. ~Louise L. Hay</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="599">"If I want to be accepted as I am, then I need to be willing to accept others as they are. ~Louise L. Hay</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="600">"A strong positive self-image is the possible preparation for success in life. ~Dr. Joyce Brothers</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="601">"As I walked out the door toward my freedom, I knew that if I did not leave all the anger, hatred and bitterness behind, that I would still be in PRISON. ~ NelsonMandela</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="602">"People are not lazy. They simply have impotent goals – that is, goals that do not inspire them. ~Tony Robbins</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="603">"Everything should be made as simple as possible, but not simpler. ~Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="604">"The only reason for time is so that everything doesn’t happen at once. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="605">"Not everything that counts can be counted, and not everything that can be counted counts. ~Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="606">"Everybody is a genius. But if you judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree, it will live its whole life believing that it is stupid. ~Albert Einstein</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="607">"Anger is never without reason but seldom with a good one. ~Benjamin Franklin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="608">"A slip of the foot you may soon recover, but a slip of the tongue you may never get over. ~Benjamin Franklin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="609">"Remember not only to say the right thing in the right place, but far more difficult still, to leave unsaid the wrong thing at the tempting moment. ~Benjamin Franklin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="610">"A house is not a home unless it contains food and fire for the mind as well as the body. ~ Benjamin Franklin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="611">"If you tell the truth, you don’t have to remember anything. ~Mark Twain</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="612">"It is never too late to be what you might have been. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="613">"It takes a great deal of bravery to stand up to our enemies, but just as much to stand up to our friends. ~J.K. Rowling</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="614">"Do not pity the dead, Harry. Pity the living, and, above all those who live without love. ~J.K. Rowling,</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="615">"A reader lives a thousand lives before he dies. The man who never reads lives only one. ~George R.R. Martin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="616">"Never forget what you are, for surely the world will not. Make it your strength. Then it can never be your weakness. Armour yourself in it, and it will never be used to hurt you. ~George R.R. Martin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="617">"Ten years from now, no one is going to care how quickly the books came out. The only thing that will matter, the only thing anyone will remember, is how good they were. That’s my main concern, and always will be. ~George R. R. Martin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="618">"They can keep their heaven. When I die, I’d sooner go to Middle Earth. ~George R.R. Martin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="619">"The great thing about reading is that it broadens your life. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="620">"We all need to be mocked from time to time, lest we take ourselves too seriously. ~ George R.R. Martin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="621">"Do what you can, with what you have, where you are. ~Theodore Roosevelt</Quotes>
    </Chasing_Dream>
    <business>
        <Quotes id="622">"Ever since happiness heard your name, it’s been running through the streets trying to find you. ~Hafiz</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="623">"Run my dear from anything that may not strengthen your precious budding wings. ~Hafiz</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="624">"I wish I could show you when you are lonely or in darkness, the Astonishing Light of your own being. ~ Hafiz</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="625">"In every end, there is also a beginning. ~Libba Bray</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="626">"Being listened to is so much like being loved that most people can’t tell the difference. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="627">"What you do speaks so loudly that I cannot hear what you say. ~Ralph Waldo Emerson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="628">"There is only one success: to be able to spend your life in your own way. ~Christopher Morley</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="629">"The difference between ordinary and extraordinary is that little extra. ~Jimmy Johnson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="630">"Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="631">"To avoid criticism, do nothing, say nothing, be nothing. ~Elbert Hubbard</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="632">"The question isn’t who is going to let me; it’s who is going to stop me. ~Ayn Rand</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="633">"The best way to predict the future is to create it. ~Peter Drucker</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="634">"When it’s time to die, let us not discover that we have never lived. ~Henry David Thoreau</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="635">"Good is the enemy of great. And that’s one of the key reasons why we have so little that becomes great. ~Jim Collins</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="636">"If you don’t design your own life plan, chances are you’ll fall into someone else’s plan. And guess what they have planned for you? Not much. ~ </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="637">"You can’t wait for inspiration. You have to go after it with a stick. ~Jack London</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="638">"The certainty that life cannot be long, and the probability that it will be much shorter than nature allows, ought to awaken every man to the active prosecution of whatever he is desirous to perform. ~Samuel Jackson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="639">"Alexander Pope once wrote that the theater aspires to wake the soul by gentle strokes of art – to raise the genius and to mend the heart. ~Kelsey Grammar as Dr. Frasier Crane, TV show</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="640">"When one door closes, another opens but there’s often a long hallway in between. ~Ric Jarow</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="641">"You must find a place inside yourself where nothing is impossible. ~Deepak Chopra</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="642">"Don’t let a bad day make you think that you have a bad life. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="643">"I am always doing that which I cannot do, in order that I may learn how to do it. – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="644">"Take care of your body. It’s the only place you have to live. – Jim Rohn</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="645">"We do not remember days. We remember moments. – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="646">"Speak the truth even if your voice shakes – Unknown</Quotes>
    </business>
    <success>
        <Quotes id="647">"In the end, these things matter most: How well did you love? How fully did you live? How deeply did you let go? ~Gautama Buddha</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="648">"The only thing worth writing about is the human heart in conflict with itself. ~William Faulkner</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="649">"Forgive yourself for what you didn’t know until you learned it. ~Zig Ziglar</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="650">"Nothing haunts us like the things we don’t say. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="651">"The world breaks everyone, and afterward, some are strong at the broken places. ~Ernest Hemingway</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="652">"It’s difficult to pursue a dream. It’s a tragedy not to. ~Oprah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="653">"Talent is God-given, be humble. Fame is man-given, be grateful. Conceit is self-given, be careful. ~Oprah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="654">"Surround yourself only with people who are going to lift you higher. ~Oprah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="655">"You can have it all. Just not all at once. ~Oprah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="656">"Always give without remembering. Always receiving without forgetting. ~Oprah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="657">"Professor Johnston often said that if you didn’t know history, you didn’t know anything. You were a leaf that didn’t know it was part of a tree. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="658">"There were never any good old days. They are today, they are tomorrow. It’s a stupid thing we say, cursing tomorrow in sorrow. ~Gogol Bordell</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="659">"Transformation is an endless process meant to be lived. It cannot be captured or possessed; you can only participate in it. ~ Baron Baptiste</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="660">"Nothing is as fatiguing as the eternal hanging on of an uncompleted task. -William James</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="661">"You go faster the slower you go and the longer the slow the smoother the strokes. ~Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="662">"It doesn’t interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart’s longing. ~Oriah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="663">"Better that the whole world should turn against you… than you should consent to turn against what is true within you. ~ </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="664">"Remembering that you are going to die is the best way I know to avoid the trap of thinking that you have something to lose. You are already naked. There is no reason to not follow your heart. ~Steve Jobs</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="665">"If we have been pleased with life, then we should not be displeased with death since it comes from the hand of the same master. ~Michelangelo</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="666">"Once in a while it really hits people that they don’t have to experience the world in the way they have been told to. ~Alan Keightle</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="667">"You look at someone long enough, you discover their humanity. ~Jack Nicholson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="668">"You’re only given a little spark of madness, you mustn’t lose it. ~</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="669">"If you realized how powerful your thoughts are, you would never think a negative thought. ~Peace Pilgrim</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="670">"You’ve gotta dance like there’s nobody watching, love like you’ll never be hurt, sing like there’s nobody listening, and live like it’s heaven on earth.” ― </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="671">"“Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten.”― Neil Gaiman</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="672">"“Everything you can imagine is real.”― Pablo Picasso</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="673">"“When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us.” ― Helen Keller</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="674">"“Do one thing every day that scares you.”― </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="675">"“It’s no use going back to yesterday, because I was a different person then.”― Lewis Carroll</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="676">"“Smart people learn from everything and everyone, average people from their experiences, stupid people already have all the answers.” – Socrates</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="677">"“Do what you feel in your heart to be right – for you’ll be criticized anyway.”― Eleanor Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="678">"“Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions.” ― Dalai Lama XIV</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="679">"“Whatever you are, be a good one.” ― </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="680">"“The same boiling water that softens the potato hardens the egg. It’s what you’re made of. Not the circumstances.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="681">"“If we have the attitude that it’s going to be a great day it usually is.” – Catherine Pulsifier</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="682">"Just another Magic Monday” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="683">"“One day or day one. You decide.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="684">"“It’s Monday… time to motivate and make dreams and goals happen. Let’s go!” – Heather Stillufsen</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="685">"There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed. ~ </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="686">"Spring has passed. Summer has gone. Winter is here…and the song I meant to sing remains unsung … for I have spent my days stringing and unstringing my instrument. ~Rabindranath Tagore</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="687">"If we leave our smells behind when we leave a room, surely something of our soul must remain when we leave this life. ~George R.R. Martin</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="688">"“It was a Monday and they walked on a tightrope to the sun.”― Marcus Zusak</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="689">"“Goodbye blue Monday.” ― </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="690">"“So. Monday. We meet again. We will never be friends—but maybe we can move past our mutual enmity toward a more-positive partnership.” ― Julio-Alexi Genao</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="691">"“When life gives you Monday, dip it in glitter and sparkle all day.” – Ella Woodword</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="692">"Monday c’est Mon Day</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="693">"All Motivation Mondays need are a little more coffee and a lot more mascara</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="694">"“You can either experience the pain of discipline or the pain of regret. The choice is yours.”&amp;nbsp; – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="695">"“Impossible is just an opinion.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="696">"“Your passion is waiting for your courage to catch up.” – Isabelle Lafleche</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="697">"“Magic is believing in yourself. If you can make that happen, you can make anything happen.” – Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="698">"“If something is important enough, even if the odds are stacked against you, you should still do it.” – Elon Musk</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="699">"“Hold the vision, trust the process.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="700">"“Don’t be afraid to give up the good to go for the great.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="701">"“People who wonder if the glass is half empty or full miss the point. The glass is refillable.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="702">"No one is to blame for your future situation but yourself. If you want to be successful, then become “Successful.”― Jaymin Shah</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="703">"I have decided to stick with love. Hate is too great a burden to bear. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="704">"Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about the things that matter. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="705">"Darkness cannot drive out darkness. Only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate. Only love can do that. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="706">"“Things may come to those who wait, but only the things left by those who hustle.”― Abraham Lincoln</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="707">"“Everything comes to him who hustles while he waits.”― Thomas Edison</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="708">"We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act, but a habit.” – Aristotle</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="709">"“If you’re offered a seat on a rocket ship, don’t ask what seat! Just get on.” –</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="710">"“I always did something I was a little not ready to do. I think that’s how you grow. When there’s that moment of ‘Wow, I’m not really sure I can do this,’ and you push through those moments, that’s when you have a breakthrough.” – Marissa Mayer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="711">"“If you hear a voice within you say ‘you cannot paint,’ then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced.” – Vincent Van Gogh</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="712">"“How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world.” – Anne Frank</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="713">"“Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen.” – Michael Jordan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="714">"The hard days are what make you stronger.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="715">"“If you believe it’ll work out, you’ll see opportunities. If you don’t believe it’ll work out, you’ll see obstacles.” – Wayne Dyer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="716">"“Keep your eyes on the stars, and your feet on the ground.” – Theodore Roosevelt</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="717">"“You can waste your lives drawing lines. Or you can live your life crossing them.” – Shonda Rhimes</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="718">"“You’ve got to get up every morning with determination if you’re going to go to bed with satisfaction.” – George Lorimer</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="719">"“I now tried a new hypothesis: It was possible that I was more in charge of my happiness than I was allowing myself to be.” – Michelle Obama</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="720">"“In a gentle way, you can shake the world.” – Mahatma Gandhi</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="721">"“Every sucessful person in the world is a hustler one way or another. We all hustle to get where we need to be. Only a fool would sit around and wait on another man to feed him.” ― K’wan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="722">"“Invest in your dreams. Grind now. Shine later.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="723">"“Hustlers don’t sleep, they nap.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="724">"“Greatness only comes before hustle in the dictionary.” – Ross Simmonds</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="725">"“Without hustle, talent will only carry you so far.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="726">"“Work like there is someone working twenty four hours a day to take it away from you.” – Mark Cuban</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="727">"“Hustle in silence and let your success make the noise.” – Unknown</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="728">"In the end, we will remember not the words of our enemies but the silence of our friends. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="729">"Keep your face always toward the sunshine, and shadows will fall behind you. ~Walt Whitman</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="730">"All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.” – Walt Disney</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="731">"“The secret of getting ahead is getting started.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="732">"“I’ve missed more than 9,000 shots in my career. I’ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times I’ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I’ve failed over and over and over again in my life and that is why I succeed.” – Michael Jordan</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="733">"&amp;nbsp;“If opportunity doesn’t knock, build a door.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="734">"“Don’t be pushed around by the fears in your mind. Be led by the dreams in your heart.” – Roy T. Bennett</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="735">"“Work hard in silence, let your success be the noise.” – Frank Ocean</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="736">"“Great things are done by a series of small things brought together” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="737">"“If you hire people just because they can do a job, they’ll work for your money. But if you hire people who believe what you believe, they’ll work for you with blood and sweat and tears.” – Simon Sinek</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="738">"“Very often, a change of self is needed more than a change of scene.’ – A.C. Benson</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="739">"“Leaders can let you fail and yet not let you be a failure.” – Stanley McChrystal</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="740">"“It’s not the load that breaks you down, it’s the way you carry it.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="741">"Don’t say you don’t have enough time. You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were given to Helen Keller, Pasteur, Michelangelo, Mother Teresa, Leonardo Da Vinci, Thomas Jefferson, and Albert Einstein.” – H. Jackson Brown Jr.</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="742">"“Hard work beats talent when talent doesn’t work hard.” – Tim Notke</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="743">"“If everything seems to be under control, you’re not going fast enough.” – Mario Andretti</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="744">"“Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work.” – Thomas Edison</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="745">"“The only difference between ordinary and extraordinary is that little extra.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="746">"“The best way to appreciate your job is to imagine yourself without one.” – Oscar Wilde</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="747">"“Unsuccessful people make their decisions based on their current situations. Successful people make their decisions based on where they want to be.” – Benjamin Hardy</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="748">"“Never stop doing your best just because someone doesn’t give you credit.” – Kamari aka Lyrikal</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="749">"“Work hard for what you want because it won’t come to you without a fight. You have to be strong and courageous and know that you can do anything you put your mind to. If somebody puts you down or criticizes you, just keep on believing in yourself and turn it into something positive.” – Leah LaBelle “Work hard, be kind, and amazing things will happen.” – Conan O’Brien</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="750">"“Don’t limit yourself. Many people limit themselves to what they think they can do. You can go as far as your mind lets you. What you believe, remember, you can achieve.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="751">"“The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.” – Chinese Proverb</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="752">"“Only the paranoid survive.” – Andy Grove</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="753">"“It’s hard to beat a person who never gives up.” – </Quotes>
        <Quotes id="754">"“I wake up every morning and think to myself, ‘how far can I push this company in the next 24 hours.’” – Leah Busque</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="755">"“If people are doubting how far you can go, go so far that you can’t hear them anymore.” – Michele Ruiz</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="756">"“We need to accept that we won’t always make the right decisions, that we’ll screw up royally sometimes – understanding that failure is not the opposite of success, it’s part of success.” – Arianna Huffington</Quotes>
        <Quotes id="757">"“Write it. Shoot it. Publish it. Crochet it, sauté it, whatever. MAKE.” – Joss Whedon</Quotes>
    </success>

</Motivational_Quotes>